welcome welcome welcome welcome
we make sure don't everything up on my
computer that I can't show you guys no
it is not like that it is not clickbait
you know I wouldn't do that to y'all you
know I wouldn't do that to y'all it's
not laggy skokie Sunday this is high
quality Skokie Sunday shit wait
do mi o fi who's here from my Wi-Fi yeah
my wife asked
no no clickbait okay guys if you're
watching this periscope right now if you
go on the shop at shop taka Medina and
you add a midnight black Aeon to your
cart hang on
oh we can even apply the discount
multiple times per order it's fine oh
yeah $100 off
with the code labor day bro
there was no upgrade program no no no no
no no so this is only active through
Labor Day if you were thinking of buying
a midnight black Aeon I think we'll ship
we'll probably ship Tuesday cuz it's a
holiday oh no we don't sell spray paint
no no no no um but if you use that code
for day bro alright so maybe here's
something else we should uh we should
talk about
so let's first tweet about that which
treat about that is there promote get a
shareable link yeah I got tabs bro get
$100 all midnight black let me make sure
I get the capitalization right you know
you gotta get the subtlety right you
guys you gotta get the subtlety right
$100 off oh yeah no no it's all capital
midnight black beyond - cab dev kit
that's right let me just make sure this
link works oh you know no the link only
kind of works
oh well good enough with
with the code labor J bro buy it soon
discount over tomorrow night shop calm
about AI that's right code labor day bro
at checkout let me see if this actually
works I don't know I've never actually
used a coupon code on our website before
let's continue to check out discount
code let's try it
Labor Day bro let me show you
don't midnight black yonder my car I'm
gonna apply the discount code Labor Day
bro
oh yeah $100 off look at that look at
that $100 off at check-out not chicken
clothes
check out buy it soon discount over
tomorrow night
wait what plant multiple times bullshit
if you cheat we cancel your order cuz
that's how we were all Akane I know you
can't apply it multiple times what I
think you can do I think if you add more
than one to your car you get the
discount applied to all of them yep yep
yep that's right that's right
I two of them you still get this 200
it's $100 off each midnight black
because we want to incentivize think
there isn't even 100 in stock there are
100 midnight black eons left in the
world you get yours today
and you'll be happy you don't get yours
today you'll be sad but it soon discount
over tomorrow night lowest price in
history
exclamation point lowest price in
history exclamation point
yeah why so low guys it's Labor Day you
know it's not Labor Day with you you
know how much I love America
midnight blanking you I miss nice it's
got lots of space for long drives what
models next after they sell out well
price ISM prices only go up bot you got
but yeah price is only and it's even
lower with your affiliate link yes
that's true you can go crazy don't go
posting affiliate links on the slack but
you know we're trying we're trying to
get our user numbers up I mean uh you
know what wait
no see no I capitalized it wrong it's
terrible we got we got to delete this
tweet so much space for drives we will
also include midnight black yawn dashcam
dev kit buy it soon discount over
tomorrow night so much space for drives
lowest price in history so much space
for drives lowest price in history
that's right shop I don't got anything
using Twitter watching me on periscope
just counting over tomorrow night so
much space for drives lowest price in
history yeah
that light eyebrow but ya know get yours
and get yours today who's a bot I'll be
on the bottom because they wanted the
real question is why hasn't periscope
caught on to this pattern check it out
Annie made me tea I'm gonna drink it
tastes delicious thank you Andy wait but
now I don't know if you end your message
with a heart you might be a bot oh now I
understand why periscope doesn't bit
yeah I know
guys I know where periscopes of dying
platforms should we move to youtube live
is that what we should move to look at
we got more followers on Twitter how
much follows is label half so that's our
followers 17.2 way way mo twitter
alright alright guys we can beat way
ball was caught up to we can also beat
way mo and miles so Wavell has 9 million
miles we have is it up to 5.3 million
yet oh yeah it is we have 5.3 2 million
miles so we are more than halfway to a
window to ship for miles really count
yes I did yeah we got all the miles
most of them honestly today open-top
miles this is a panda you guys know the
pandas I wish we sold more pandas we
need to sell panthous is that a bot I
don't even know that's kind of it
see like look now that we talked about
the hard thing
these are pandas by a neon HealthBeat
way mo today is the best day to get in
with the midnight black you know I'm
Michelle that's why we go on periscope
we got a shill for that buy that Merc
you know
has anyone used the code yet no users of
the code yet sales and good guys sounds
that be good we've been we've been you
know July was the highest sales month on
record for , August was really close see
how close August was now damn me why not
have remote-control driver like way mo
regulators feel comfortable don't worry
by that merge by that verse doesn't Jay
Paul song you know Jake Palmer song it's
a great song actually merge song all I
want for Christmas
well I didn't even know it had a video
[Music]
guys honestly the pawls are kind of
cringe-worthy now they were cool last
year
you all know when Logan Paul was cool
he's not cool anymore we're over Logan
Paul don't worry don't worry we're not
going there we're going to talk about
self-driving cars today um I was driving
around in my uh my Honda Accord this
week and I've been I've been happy it's
pretty good guys oh I was talking to my
friend yesterday and I'm like I'm
talking about how I got sunburned right
you know I got sunburned I wanted a
sailing trip and I got really badly
sunburned because the water doesn't
block the sunburn because the Sun burns
you with UV not with infrared infrared
is heat so the water does block the heat
but it doesn't block the UV now an
interesting side effect of water
blocking IR it means that light ARS
don't work in the rain and ladders also
don't work not even in the rain but just
when things are wet oh you're pretty
sure I got ADHD bro let me see your
medical degree
you got medical degree bro oh you got a
summer from welding yes that UV right uh
no you're not giving a summer from lie
down lie down won't sunburn you just
will never work in the rain a way to
avoid regressions during releases guys
um so yeah this is the rolls we're
hiring for right now right down here um
I've given up like when I release
engineers in firmware anymore those are
kind of ridiculous rolls actually there
aren't really real but we're hiring a
test engineer we're hiring an m/l
engineer or hiring someone to come work
on explore in Cabana um if you've seen
exploring Cabana they could always use
more love the other little third they're
a little janky and we want to be better
here's another here's another
interesting thing to think about you
know I've been asking you guys on slack
we're trying to get to a thousand daily
active
users have it asked you guys what you
want general things are more stability
less battery I don't care if you have a
comp side degree you can go to our
github and you'll find this repo called
speed challenge if you do well on that
challenge I'll hire you no matter what I
don't I don't care about anything else
unless you're weird real high or weird
people
now I'm kidding everyone here is weird a
vision a CC of a challenge is the its
speed prediction challenge so we give
your video predict the speed of the car
from the challenge no no no I'm weird
Braille look at me I'm a weird I have
ADHD that guy said so oh no we don't do
adjustable following distances it's not
safe
so some of those cars will let you
adjust the following distance is
something that's really small um if you
right now with our following distance VG
still works here absolutely um if you
adjust the following distance to be too
short you won't have enough time to
react if the car makes a mistake so
that's why we fix the following distance
to one thing salary equity yes we have
both of those look if you're trying to
come here and like oh I'm gonna get paid
a crazy high salary oh you know oh I'm
gonna make equity and I'm gonna be rich
then and then and then that you're
missing the point I mean you might do
those things look if we win when we win
I mean I don't know like guys you see
that you saw the way motion right turns
out like we've always mostly fake news
and doesn't really work like obviously I
said at my medium folks you know uh how
many scope is that we hired we've hired
two people from the community obviously
you know VG was talked about and someone
else so we've three main focuses one of
them is a secret which we can't talk
about it one of them is Maps you know
we're doing maps by the end of the year
if you get hired can you get in a
private round
Oh like investment I don't want any more
investment we got the best terms from
VCS who cares and our third our third is
daily active users so daily active users
maps and super-secret projects you know
that's true that's true you guys know
you guys know who's here um yeah oh man
has anyone used that coupon code yet
okay have you use that coupon code yeah
go work for him if you want a big salary
that's good
someone did buy something our t-shirt we
saw the t-shirt oh yeah it's plenty you
you will live comfortably it's starting
salaries are like over Harvick a crude
for software you can live in SF
comfortably I mean that's a thing right
like you know wait you're a bot you
thought way Mo's the furthest ahead I
mean the furthest ahead towards what
right
I don't think way Moe's business model
works I think that their cars are way
too finicky and way too expensive the
Civic tremor hack right now you know
what needs a firmware hack the Accord
drive around the Accord all weekend two
things the Bosch ACC is great on the
highway
no I lie you know the transparency thing
is all I we're all chills and hype here
it's all it's all lies no but uh the box
as you see it's good on the highway I
was happy with it on the highway but
it's stopping behind a stopped car is
it's it's terrible so I'm just like I'm
uncomfortable yeah I want to stand firm
we're have for my Accord to because
somebody get on that weight Accord go on
how much of a technical challenge is
firmware happening how many ml people do
we have all right so there's no teams
here like we don't have teams we have
individual roles like everyone here is
an individual contributor the problem
with team
is the dilution of responsibility right
um but you know this is kind of why I
don't like working on teams like if I'm
like three people are on the same
project it's terrible because you spend
most your time communicating with people
unless you're time coding it's much less
efficient then you know just sitting
down coding so yeah I mean our ml people
are more so we'd make the model you
could work on the model a big model you
guys know about big model I talk about
big model big mall is pretty cool no we
got rid of the recruiter recruiting was
kind of dumb um this is this is big
model yo big models sick okay all right
I'll show you guys I'll show you guys
something since you're all here on the
periscope so this is the model that's
currently shipped on the car this is our
like internal model tracking tool it has
a validation loss of negative two point
five nine three so you can see this is
how it trained this is big model big
model has a validation loss of negative
three point two three five crazy guys
big model also little model has 1
million weights big model has 23 million
weights no toll cars actually the
problem with the rav4 we thought it was
the model but it's not
it was calibration and that's why we
shipped new fast calibration I hope you
guys are enjoying that what alright
alright no racist shit roomy cab is a
bot next time roomie cam talks I will
ban them
what the hell was this all right we got
we got we've got a no racism policy in
the periscope raises get bad that's
right get out of my periscope advantage
is a big model other than more weight so
big model so little model only looks at
little part of the screen big model
looks at big part of the screen um big
model big model trains on crazy amounts
of data I can let me show ya bring up I
got some infrastructure here so big
model
six point two terabytes of data big data
browse this periscope broken did I come
up with a big model name ten big t1f no
oh it's not as great I was driving
around in hentai I should I should have
brought you guys I was driving out with
you and I Thursday night binary exploits
you've written for Mac OS your band
Batman let's say and we're commonly as
Batman you come here you get to be
Batman you're a bot Wow
my periscope is full of like BOTS and
races and terrible stuff tonight band
man that's right we drop in the hammer
let's uh do I have a midnight by the
young we can look at this is my young
she's my young Cinna young that's black
screws as we mark the internal ones um
the car manufacturers can't walk me out
remember that Apple and Sony couldn't
lock me out big models not in production
um big model doesn't fit on the on e on
quite we got a shrink big model we got
to take big model and then do weight
shrinking does midnight black get hot in
sunlight not any hotter than the other
Eon I know some of you guys have been
talking about yeah the thermal issues if
you keep it plugged in and you get a
comma power you always have power it
will run the fan even when the cars not
on so that does pretty good things for
the battery campus encryption yeah way
he's touring the key small big model
yeah you're the small big model right
you think it's an oxymoron but it's real
shit how big is the binary the model so
this new big model is 23 million weights
so the current model that shipping
about a million weights so it's a little
over money so it's like 20 times bigger
don't worry don't worry big model will
run on midnight black eons and normal
eons yeah I've never had thermal issues
either but it's for people and we keep
all the eons in the car but it's for
people in hotter areas you know where it
gets up to like 95 do we use GPU no we
only make model on CPU no Krispies you
want to see you guys here training
computer lessons ancient or any computer
oh here we are at my prompt ssh GPU
slave double zero yeah look at them we
got ten we've got ten ten sixties in
there they're working on training a
different big model right now where I'm
playing with some high prefer a meters
I'm playing I'm removing the dropout and
seeing if we have enough gated actually
just not used dropout at all I didn't
write it it's called Nvidia semi but
yeah so we got we got an army of GPUs
down there
oh the comment ASCII oh yeah yeah go
sorry for the masses right we got yeah
these are timid ease yeah we have we
have 10/10 ATT eyes in this box you
thought inside was too many secrets yeah
well I hate some of the secrets when and
how did I learn them now you guys will
see when big model comes out um new
calibration is is probably you'll see
you'll see what harmonica do it's it's
cool the other thing that we're working
on is the cutting problem so small model
can't see the cuttings but big model
should be able to big model should be
able to see if there's a car merging
over into your legs the radar has a very
narrow field of view
um the camera neon has a pretty wide
field here it's actually like 70 degrees
so it's enough to see cuttings but the
model right now can't see them because
it's small model you know everything is
better in big model big model and it's
also it's a much more modern machine
learning architecture so like small
model is not that different from the one
we started out with when Connie I
started big mall is a its exception it's
based on exception so we got those what
do they call those stupid convolutions
depth-wise separable convolutions so you
have I could calm if you have like a
three by three columns
and it has a bunch of channels can it
play crisis that doesn't matter
oh yeah people merging in yeah I know
we're doing that
what's the predicted support timeframe
for an eon who said there was support
did someone tell you there was support
someone lied you know moving to a new
one plus model no no no no so the the
Aeon put this way the Aeon compatible
code base will be sold all through next
year as well we can definitely fix
cartons with video I'm kid big mobile
identify box sorry that's not with big
model is turned on you are by I can
identify bot so I have really big
hundred trillion ways is crazy
why do you think the camera aperture has
anything to do with the Sun yeah we'll
see well we'll see we'll see what I'll
have one go by what skills required for
the ML engineer well ml and engineering
with GPS coming into play no we're gonna
do maps first right so we do have apps
this year and then the Aeons will
hopefully start using maps but you know
if you for open piled 0.6 if and when
open 0.6 comes to eon you're gonna need
a great panda yeah I really don't think
the aperture things a problem
the focus algorithm could be a little
bit better yeah that's pretty good
amines actually but yeah by panda by UN
that shop comedy I tensorflow required
denim out we use chorus which features
are using in your maps lanes and the
same as the super good map if you check
out like our map stuff it's similar to
that
we have like ley lines and paths and all
that stuff
our gray panda works on Mercedes I don't
even know what that means you can stick
a gray panda in the Mercedes it'll work
I guess maps topside the big model new
hardware stop signs yes thousands in
traffic cuts yeah yeah those will happen
someday
no you can't train your white panda for
gray panda you can buy a great panda for
$1.99 you can also wait you know you can
you can just buy the eon you can buy the
grab handle later we have we have a
bunch in stock so great pandas will be
around for a while they'll be sold well
into next year pandas are gonna be sold
for the lifetime combo you know many of
these things we have I'll tell you how
many pairs you think we have all the
column please protect you what are we
doing with the rest of our white Oh what
feature descriptors it's uh a bunch of
different things or yeah we do we have
10,000 pandas I have boxes and boxes of
pandas so pandas we got lots of them
think about pandas firmwares open sores
it only gets better with time I'd like
to hire somebody to make the firm but
panda firm or even better is this is
this some affiliate marketing going on
in my twitch channel sorry sorry
periscope I gotta I gotta keep it
straight I mean you guys know just like
GB ASMR has another channel on twitch
tree that's a twitch comment I gotta I
gotta stick to the periscope we're here
to talk yeah Jesse Jesse definitely made
some good contributions to to the Panda
firmware will you give any extra white
pandas to needy zoos honestly if a su
sent me an application I would think
about it we tried to partner with Panda
Express to sell the pandas who was Neil
McNeil still exists Oh pandas are
indestructible guys don't worry
about that what would improve Panda
firmware Joe I don't know like something
I'm not sure what Pam's do right now no
like we need better elm support and
better J shit support so it works with
like the manufacturer tools yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
when does the comma pop-up store
please make cabana functional yeah well
we're hiring somebody you want to come
here and work here make cavanna
functional and every nice so they're not
work videos broken andy the scobie's are
saying cabaas broken let's see if i can
get to the great is the test a longer in
Cabana wait what is this cabanas broken
let me smoke him little smoke on
periscope sometime we spoke on twitch
what video doesn't work
hang on I'll ping Andy scope ease are
saying video broke in Cabana it broke
when he fixed little-endian really Oh
Explorer looks nice guys this is this is
my Explorer
my drive in the Civic 1+3
yeah I don't know why these ones aren't
loading that could be better
my Explorer is looking sexy like this
takes forever to load was the hide why
hasn't it loaded yet I don't know how do
I open open in Cabana video works fine
for me guys I don't know what you're
talking about video works fine I don't
know why it's a laggy but like as
Explorer is using tons of stuff but yeah
the video vitiates fun
guys I just went to this videos fine
load up my Civic DV stay
all videos broken in shared drives we
gotta be specific
oh it's just the demo drive okay this
Dopey's are saying you guys I'm trying
to fix your problems now I'm thinking
about I'm thinking about ya Bugsy checks
slack message and see we got here
yeah you're right there's no video I
hang on alright I've done my part of
sending that link to relevant people
[Music]
Australian X for most Eon whoa whoa you
guys uh how was fake news I'm back I'll
show us ridiculous job requests do you
want to go through we were having a good
time responding to some LinkedIn
messages Australia needs to lobby the
government to drive on the right side of
the road with the EO not benefit by
going to the why not no no it's not
happening it's not happening to
expensive you guys phones got too
expensive here we have like this Eon it
looks like there's like vadi on top like
we're not looking at that Eon right now
but get your midnight blacks it is gonna
be the cheapest way to get a 128 kg on
if you want a 128 kg on so make sure to
get in and get that the code is Labor
Day bro yeah that's no good not sure
what the issue is they're just looking
since you mention it yeah cool
yawn too should just get a price bump
well yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean we
talked a lot about the price point I'm
not sure a higher price point would be
particularly good you guys are gonna be
priced similarly similarly to what to
what we've been doing and we can't
really do it if we use new phones
if they also really wouldn't help that
much I mean a lot of the problem with
the phone is the battery we don't really
want the battery but it's in the phone
can we get the battery out of the phone
unless your kitty pryde phase-in
take the battery
solid gold a on gold is a metal it
conducts heat I don't know if that's
good or bad it was a specific heat of
gold all right Scott that was a very
upbeat skull piece under who likes copy
Sunday so we do Moore's copy Sunday's
you're a bot you ruins copy Sunday is SF
region most eon sold no that's not true
all over America well one of these days
the bots are gonna start calling out the
bots and I'm gonna be like it's the bots
you can't even tell anymore like two
BOTS come in one bot pulls out the other
BOTS you ban the bat bot common still
absolutely has a chef working a comma is
a great experience it will change your
life
yeah
those things well I hire you if you
write a balk detector now I'll hire you
if you do out on our programming
challenge we got some good results from
our face detection program a challenge
that's how we have the driver mom right
now
never mind pretty good thanks floor is
really nice okay liking Explorer I
thought it was worse it's pretty decent
I can choose from all our these are all
our company cars
you know what's a neon gold I don't know
Prius
what no one's been driving the Prius oh
that only just doesn't work yeah the
rav4 it's just been sitting there
there's a bit of Mexico when I rename
this every name and it device device
name Oh share by human I don't even know
what that does Oh what were the bad
submissions of the programming challenge
I don't know something we'll just do so
badly I don't know why there's all this
orange as well where's me driving around
in the Accord that's me
for some nice drives yesterday
oh yeah Gordian gold said that oh yeah
me dropping my friend off this morning
yeah this version of Explorer is public
I'm just from by that coming out of AI
seems everything else isn't me driving
my friend's house only engaged a little
bit
yeah cool thank you
none of people know about my that coming
oh yeah yeah cuz I don't market chips
marketing for losers um oh you didn't
know that might not comment on it I oh
it's nice feel like you support a
vehicle with less than 400 horsepower or
more than 400 horsepower I think you can
download up we're looking into the
Cabana issue right now I think you can
download more horsepower for your Accord
you didn't know that might not come
about I
promote it much yeah this might outcome
another guy you can see like lucky you
see if the model doesn't work here
because we need big model I was engaged
here so it clearly was working this was
pleasant
pleasantly driving through West Portal
someone to load was the stuff why is it
loaded yet let's take this off
you are bad you're a bot
you've been anywhere you're not real put
a link on the homepage he had we could
put a link on the homepage that sounds
kind of nice I wish she'd kind of shell
for explore on our homepage yes probably
good idea I don't know man
see why disengage there
why did this engage here guys because
cuz we came up on a red light I look at
that red light yeah reason I needed to
take over for safety I wanted to take
home oh that's a little I don't know I
feel about that speed limits with big
model or Maps speed limits be part of
maps
you know maps are coming maps of all
highways all the other states in America
we're gonna roll about I thank you for
joining us Cobie Sunday that's been 40
minutes
I'm going out to get a pizza cuz I love
pizza I hope you all have a great Labor
Day thank you
ground loop I appreciate that wait'll
you see what's in the store calming eyes
got a bright future ahead of it we're
happy to have all you with us
vice Kobe's